<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Researchers on Department of Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/eng/teams/researchers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Researchers on Department of Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:39:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/eng/teams/researchers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chung-Kyu Park</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/jkpark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/jkpark/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-interests&#34;&gt;Research interests&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Climate prediction and analysis&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Asian monsoon and drought&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Climate change science and adaptation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Urban climate and air quality&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;Education&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ph.D. (1987) Department of Atmospheric Sciences, University of Missouri-Columbia, MO, USA&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;M.S. (1980) Department of Astronomy and Meteorology, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;B.S. (1978) Department of Astronomy and Meteorology, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-experience&#34;&gt;Research Experience&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sept 2020 -present &#x9;Professor extraordinary, Department of Atmospheric sciences, Yonsei University&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mar 2013 – Aug 2020&#x9;Director, Regional Office for Asia and the South-West Pacific, World Meteorological Organization (WMO)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mar 2009 - Feb 2013&#x9;Director-General, Planning &amp;amp; Coordination Bureau, Met Industry &amp;amp; Information and Telecommunication Bureau, Climate Science Bureau, Korea Meteorological Administration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Apr 2008 - Feb 2009&#x9;Director-General, Metropolitan Air Quality Management Office, Ministry of Environment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sep 2005 - Apr 2008&#x9;Executive Director, APEC Climate Center&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mar 1987-Dec 1996&#x9;Senior scientist, Goddard Space Flight Center (GSFC),US National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;teaching&#34;&gt;Teaching&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;General circulation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Climate dynamics&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wang, B, JY Lee, IS. Kang, J. Shukla, JS. Kug, A. Kumar, J. Schemm, JJ. Luo, T. Yamagata and CK. Park, 2008: How accurately do coupled climate models predict the leading modes of Asian-Australian monsoon interannual variability? Climate Dynamics, 30, 605-619&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kang, H., K.-H. An, C.-K. Park, A. L. S. Solis, and K. Stitthichivapak, 2007:  Multimodel output statistical downscaling prediction of precipitation in the Philippines and Thailand, Geophys. Res. Lett., vol. 34.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kang, H. and C.-K. Park, 2007: Error analysis of dynamical seasonal predictions of summer precipitation over the East Asian-western Pacific region, Geophys. Res. Lett., 34, L13706, doi:10.1029/2007GL029392.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kryjov, V. N. and C.-K. Park, 2007: Solar modulation of the El-Niño/Southern Oscillation impact on the Northern Hemisphere annular mode, Geophys. Res. Lett., 34, L10701, doi:10.1029/2006GL028015.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kar, Sarat C., Anahit hovsepyan and C. K. Park, 2006: Economic Values of the APCN Multi-Model Ensemble Categorical Seasonal Prediction. Meteorology. Appl. 13, 267-277.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ha, K.-J., K.-S. Yun, J.-G. Jhun and C.-K. Park, 2005: Definition of Onset/Retreat and Intensity of Changma during the Boreal Summer Monsoon Season. J. Korea Meteorological Society, 41(6), 927-942.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lee, E.-J., J.-G. Jhun, and C.-K. Park, 2005: Remote connection of the northeast Asian summer rainfall variation revealed by a newly defined monsoon index. J. Climate. 18, 4381-4393&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Zhu, C., W.-S. Lee, H. Kang, and C.-K. Park, 2005: A proper monsoon index for seasonal and interannual variations of the East Asian Monsoon. Geophysical Research Letters. 32, L02811, doi:10.1029/2004GL021295&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kim, M.-K., I.-S. Kang, C.-K. Park and K.-M. Kim, 2004: Superensemble prediction of regional precipitation over Korea, International Journal of Climatology, 24(6), 777-790&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kang, I.-S, J.-Y. Lee, and C.K. Park, 2004: Potential predictability of summer mean precipitation in a dynamical season prediction system with systematic error correction. J. Climate, 17, 834-844.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ahn, J.-B., C.-K. Park and E.-S. Im, 2002: Reproduction of Regional Scale Surface air Temperature by Estimating Systematic Bias of Mesoscale Numerical Model, J. Korea Meteorological Society, 38(1), 69-80.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kang, I.-S., K. Jin, B. Wang, K.-M. Lau, J. Shukla, V. Krishnamurthy, S. D. Schubert, D. E. Wailser, W. F. Stern, A. Kitoh, G. A. Meehl, M. Kanamitsu, V. Y. Galin, V. Satyan, C.-K. Park, Y. Liu, 2002: Intercomparison of the climatological variations of Asian summer monsoon precipitation simulated by 10 GCMs. Climate Dynamics, 19, 383-395.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, C.-K., J.-D. Hwang and Y. Chun, 2001: The Expressions Related to Rain fall Recorded in the Chosun_Wangjo-Sillok. J. Korea Meteorological Society, 37(4), 433-441.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Min, S.-K., C.-K. Park, 2001: Application of Nonlinear Barotropic Primitive Equation Model to Medium Range Weather Forecast. J. Korea Metoerological Society, 37(2), 129-142.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hwang, J.-D. and C.-K. Park, 2000: Characteristics of Circulation Pattern over East Asia Associated with Heavy Rainfall Events in Korea during the Summer 1999, J. Korea Meteorological Society, 36(5), 573-582.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, C.-K., and S.D. Schubert,1997: On the nature of the 1994 East Asian summer drought. J. Climate, 10, 1056-1070.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Slingo, J.M., C.-K. Park, and others, 1996: Intraseasonal oscillations in 15 atmospheric general circulation models: results from an AMIP diagnostic subproject. Climate Dynamics, 12, 325-357&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, C.-K., M. Suarez, and S.D. Schubert, 1995: Response of zonally asymmetric flow to time-dependent tropical heating. J. Atmos. Sci., 52, 3738-3756.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Schubert, S.D., M Suarez, C.-K. Park, and S. Moorthi, 1993: GCM Simulations of Intraseasonal variability in the Pacific/North American Region. J. Atmos. Sci., 50, 1991-2007.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, C.-K., and S.D. Schubert, 1993: Remotely-forced intraseasonal oscillations over the tropical Atlantic. J. Atmos. Sci., 50, 89-103.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Schubert, S.D. C.-Y. Wu, J. Zero, J.-K. Schemm, C.-K. Park, and M Suarez, 1992: Monthly means of selected climate variables for 1985-89. NASA Memorandum 104565, 360pp.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kung, E.C., W. Min, J. Susskind, and C.-K. Park, 1992: An analysis of simulated summer blocking episodes. Q. J. Royal Meteor. Soc., 118,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Schubert, S.D. and C.-K. Park, 1991: Low-frequency intraseasonal tropical-extratropical interactions. J. Atmos. Sci., 48, 629-650.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kung, E.C., C.C. Dacamara, W.E. Baker, J. Susskind, and C.-K. Park, 1990: Simulations of winter blocking episodes using observed sea surface temperatures. Q. J. Royal Meteor. Soc., 116, 1053-1070.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Schubert, S.D.R.W. Higgins, C.-K. Park, S. Moorthi, and M Suarez, 1990: An atlas of ECMWF analyses (1980-87), Part II - second moment quantities. NASA Technical Memorandum 100762, 286pp.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Schubert, S.D.C.-K. Park, R.W. Higgins, S. Moorthi, and M Suarez, 1990: An atlas of ECMWF analyses (1980-87), Part I - first moment quantities. NASA Technical Memorandum 100747, 273pp.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, C.-K., D.M. Straus, K-M. Lau, and S.D. Schubert, 1990: An intercomparison of intraseasonal variability in general circulation models and observations. NASA Technical Memorandum 100764,121pp.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, C.-K., D.M. Straus, and K-M. Lau, 1990: An evaluation of the structure of tropical intraseasonal oscillations in three general circulation models. J. Meteor. Society of Japan, 68, 403-417.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, C.-K. and E. C. Kung, 1988: Principal components of the North American summer temperature field and the antecedent oceanic and conditions of the Northern Hemisphere. J. Meteor. Society Japan, 66, 677-690.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silvio Kalisch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/silviokalisch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/silviokalisch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-interests&#34;&gt;Research interests&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Middle Atmosphere dynamics&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Gravity Waves&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tropical atmosphere (Madden-Julian Oscillation)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sudden stratospheric warming&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;Education&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. rer. nat. (Ph.d.)&lt;/strong&gt; (2014) in Physics, University of Wuppertal / Research Center Juelich, Germany&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diplom (M.Sc.)&lt;/strong&gt; (2010) in Theoretical Physics, University of Leipzig, Leipzig, Germany&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-career&#34;&gt;Research career&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Jul. 2019 - today : Research Professor at Yonsei University, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dec. 2018 - Jun. 2019: Guest Scientist at Institute for Advanced Simulation / Jülich Research Centre, Germany (DFG grant no: KA4222/3-1)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2015 - Nov. 2018 : Postdoctoral fellow at Yonsei University, Korea (DFG grant no: KA4222/2-1)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2014 - 2015 : Postdoctoral Researcher at Research Center Juelich&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Oct. - Nov. 2012 : Guest Scientist at Yonsei University, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2010 - 2014 : PhD student at Wuppertal University / Researcher at Research Center Juelich&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2009 - 2010 : Research assistant and assistant teacher at Institute for Theoretical Physics, University of Leipzig&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kalisch, S., Kang M.-J., and Chun H.‐Y. (2018): &amp;ldquo;Impact of Convective Gravity Waves on the Tropical Middle Atmosphere During the Madden‐Julian Oscillation.&amp;rdquo; Journal of Geophysical Research: Atmospheres, 123(17), 8975-8992.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yuri Lee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/yurilee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/yurilee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-interests&#34;&gt;Research interests&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Remote sensing for precipitation estimation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;Education&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ph.d.&lt;/strong&gt;  (2017) in Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;M.Sc&lt;/strong&gt;  (2012) in Earth Science Education, Ewha Womans University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;B.Sc&lt;/strong&gt;  (2010) in Earth Science Education, Ewha Womans University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;professional-positions&#34;&gt;Professional Positions&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2017 - current : Post Doctoral researcher, Dept. of Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;awards&#34;&gt;Awards&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;(2015) Participation Award in the 1st Students Competition in Research using Meteorological Satellite Data&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lee, Y.-R., D.-B. Shin, J.-H. Kim, and H.-S. Park, 2015: Precipitation estimation over radar gap areas based on satellite and adjacent radar observations, Atmospheric Measurement Techniques, 8, 719-728.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Yoo, J.-M., Y.-R. Lee, D. Kim, S.-M. Oh, M.-J. Jeong, W.R. Stockwell, P. K. Kundu, D.-B. Shin, and S.-J. Lee, 2014: New indices for wet scavenging of air pollutants (O3, CO, NO2, SO2, and PM10) by summertime rain, Atmospheric Environment, 82, 226-237.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lee, Y.-R., J.-M. Yoo, M.-J. Jeong, Y.-I. Won, T. Hearty, and D.-B. Shin, 2013: Comparison between MODIS and AIRS/AMSU satellite-derived surface skin temperatures. Atmospheric Measurement Techniques, 6, 445-455.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hana Lee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/hanalee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/hanalee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-interests&#34;&gt;Research interests&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Estimation of Surface Solar radiation using satellite data&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ground-based measurement of surface radiation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Analysis of vertical ozone distribution in Antarctica&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;Education&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ph.D.&lt;/strong&gt; (2021) in Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;M.Sc&lt;/strong&gt; (2015) in Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;B.Sc&lt;/strong&gt; (2010) in Atmospheric Environment Sciences, Gangneung-Wonju National University, Gangwon-do, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;awards&#34;&gt;Awards&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Group Achievement Award, 2017.08, NASA &amp;ldquo;KORUS-AQ: An International Cooperative Air Quality Field Study in Korea&amp;rdquo; project&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, S. S., Cho, H. K., Koo, J. H., Lim, H., Lee, H., Kim, J., &amp;amp; Lee, Y. G. (2019). Monitoring and long-term trend of total column ozone from Dobson Spectrophotometer in Seoul (1985~ 2017). Atmosphere, 29(1), 13-20.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, H. J., Park, J. S., Kim, S. W., Chong, H., Lee, H., Kim, H., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Park, S. S. (2019). Retrieval of NO2 column amounts from ground-based hyperspectral imaging sensor measurements. Remote Sensing, 11(24), 3005.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lee, H., Kim, W., Lee, Y. G., Koo, J. H., Jung, Y., Park, S. S., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Kim, J. (2019). Broadband dependence of atmospheric transmissions in the UV and total solar radiation. Tellus B: Chemical and Physical Meteorology, 71(1), 1503513.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lee, H., Kim, W., Lee, Y. G., Kim, J., &amp;amp; Cho, H. K. (2019). Atmospheric transmission of ultraviolet and total solar radiation by clouds, aerosols, and ozone in Seoul, Korea: A comparison of semi-empirical model predictions with observations. Asia-Pacific Journal of Atmospheric Sciences, 55(2), 165-175.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chong, H., Lee, H., Koo, J. H., Kim, J., Jeong, U., Kim, W., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Park, S. S. (2018). Regional characteristics of NO2 column densities from Pandora observations during the MAPS-Seoul campaign.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Koo, J. H., Choi, T., Cho, Y., Lee, H., Kim, J., Ahn, D. H., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Lee, Y. G. (2018). The Variation in Aerosol Optical Depth over the Polar Stations of Korea. Aerosol and Air Quality Research, 18(12), 3020-3210.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Koo, J. H., Choi, T., Lee, H., Kim, J., Ahn, D. H., Kim, J., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Lee, Y. G. (2018). Total ozone characteristics associated with regional meteorology in West Antarctica. Atmospheric Environment, 195, 78-88.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, S. S., M. Lee, H. Lee, H. Lee, S.-M. Kim, and Y. G. Lee, “Estimating Cloud and Aerosol UV Modification Factors Based on Spectral Measurement from the Brewer Spectrophotometer”, Atmosphere, 2017, 8, 109, doi:10.3390/atmos8060109.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Jung, Y., H. Lee, J. Kim, Y. Cho, J. Kim, and Y. G. Lee, “Spatio-Temporal Characteristics in the Clearness Index Derived from Global Solar Radiation Observations in Korea”, Atmosphere, 2016, 7, 55, doi:10.3390/atmos7040055.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minsu Park</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/minsupark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/minsupark/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-interests&#34;&gt;Research interests&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Measurement of physical characteristics of aerosol and CCN&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;Education&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;B.Sc&lt;/strong&gt; (2012) in Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ph.D&lt;/strong&gt; (2018) in Cloud Physics, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;awards&#34;&gt;Awards&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kim, J. H., Park, M.-S., Shim, S., and Yum, S. S., (2012), On the contrast of aerosol size distribution and cloud condensation nuclei number concentrations between the east and the west of the Korean Peninsula. Atmosphere, 22, 87-96 (in Korean).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kim, J. H., Yum, S. S., Shim, S., Kim, W. J., Park, M., Kim, J.-H., Kim, M.-H., Yoon, S.-C. (2014), On the submicron aerosol distributions and CCN number concentrations in and around the Korean Peninsula. Atmos. Chem. Phys., 14, 8763–8779.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, M., Yum, S. S., Kim, J. H. (2015), Characteristics of submicron aerosol number size distribution and new particle formation events measured in Seoul, Korea, during 2004–2012. Asia-Pacific J. Atmos. Sci., 51, 1–10.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, M., Yum, S. S., Kim, N., Cha, J. W., Ryoo, S.-B. (2016), Characteristics of Aerosol and Cloud Condensation Nuclei Concentrations Measured over the Yellow Sea on a Meteorological Research Vessel, GISANG 1. Atmosphere, 26, 243–256 (in Korean).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kim, N., Park, M., Yum, S. S., Park, J. S., Song, I. H., Shin, H. J., Ahn, J. Y., Kwak, K.-H., Kim, H., Bae, G.-N. (2017), Hygroscopic properties of urban aerosols and their cloud condensation nuclei activities measured in Seoul during the MAPS-Seoul campaign. Atmos. Environ., 153, 217–232.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Schmale, J., Henning, S., Henzing, B., Keskinen, H., Sellegri, K., Ovadnevaite, J., Bougiatioti, A., Kalivitis, N., Stavroulas, I., Jefferson, A., Park, M., Schlag, P., Kristensson, A., Iwamoto, Y., Pringle, K., Reddington, C., Aalto, P., Äijälä, M., Baltensperger, U., Bialek, J., Birmili, W., Bukowiecki, N., Ehn, M., Fjæraa, A. M., Fiebig, M., Frank, G., Fröhlich, R., Frumau, A., Furuya, M., Hammer, E., Heikkinen, L., Herrmann, E., Holzinger, R., Hyono, H., Kanakidou, M., Kiendler, Scharr, A., Kinouchi, K., Kos, G., Kulmala, M., Mihalopoulos, N., Motos, G., Nenes, A., O’Dowd, C., Paramonov, M., Petäjä, T., Picard, D., Poulain, L., Prévôt, A. S. H., Slowik, J., Sonntag, A., Swietlicki, E., Svenningsson, B., Tsurumaru, H., Wiedensohler, A., Wittbom, C., Ogren, J. A., Matsuki, A., Yum, S. S., Myhre, C. L., Carslaw, K., Stratmann, F., Gysel, M. (2017), Collocated observations of cloud condensation nuclei, particle size distributions, and chemical composition, Scientific Data, 4, 170003.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Schmale, J., Henning, S., Decesari, S., Henzing, B., Keskinen, H., Paramonov, M., Sellegri, K., Ovadnevaite, J., Pöhlker, M. L., Brito, J., Bougiatioti, A., Kristensson, A., Kalivitis, N., Stavroulas, I., Carbone, S., Jefferson, A., Park, M., Schlag, P., Iwamoto, Y., Aalto, P., Äijälä, M., Bukowiecki, N., Ehn, M., Frank, G., Fröhlich, R., Frumau, A., Herrmann, E., Herrmann, H., Holzinger, R., Kos, G., Kulmala, M., Mihalopoulos, N., Nenes, A., O&amp;rsquo;Dowd, C., Petäjä, T., Picard, D., Pöhlker, C., Pöschl, U., Poulain, L., Prévôt, A. S. H., Swietlicki, E., Andreae, M. O., Artaxo, P., Wiedensohler, A., Ogren, J., Matsuki, A., Yum, S. S., Stratmann, F., Baltensperger, U., Gysel, M. 2018. Long-term cloud condensation nuclei number concentration, particle number size distribution, and chemical composition measurements at regionally representative observatories, Atmos. Chem. Phys..&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uju Shin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/shinuju/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/shinuju/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-interests&#34;&gt;Research interests&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mesoscale convective system&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Heavy precipitation systems over the Korean peninsula&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;Education&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ph.D.&lt;/strong&gt; (2019) in Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;M.Sc&lt;/strong&gt; (2010) in Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;B.Sc&lt;/strong&gt; (2008) in Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;awards&#34;&gt;Awards&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shin, U&lt;/strong&gt;, S.-H. Park, J.-S. Park, J.-H. Koo, C. Yoo, S. Kim, and J.-B. Lee (2021), Predictability of PM2.5 in Seoul based on atmospheric blocking forecasts using the NCEP global forecast system, Atmospheric Environment, 246, 118141, &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.atmosenv.2020.118141&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.atmosenv.2020.118141&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lee, T.-Y., &lt;strong&gt;U. Shin&lt;/strong&gt;, and S.-H. Park (2020), Atmospheric Structure for Convective Development in the Events of Cloud Clusters over the Korean Peninsula, Asia-Pacific J. Atmos. Sci., &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1007/s13143-020-00211-4&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1007/s13143-020-00211-4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shin, U.&lt;/strong&gt;, T.-Y. Lee, and S.-H. Park (2019), Environment and processes for heavy rainfall in the early morning over the Korean peninsula during episodes of cloud clusters associated with mesoscale troughs. J. Meteor. Soc. Japan, 97, &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.2151/jmsj.2019-036&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.2151/jmsj.2019-036&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shin, U.&lt;/strong&gt;, and T.-Y. Lee (2015), Origin, Evolution, Structure of Meso-α-scale Lows Associated with Cloud Clusters and Heavy Rainfall over the Korean Peninsula. Asia-Pacific J. Atmos. Sci., 51(3), 259−274, &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1007/s13143-015-0076-3&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1007/s13143-015-0076-3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yong-Jin Tak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/yongjintack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/yongjintack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-interests&#34;&gt;Research interests&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Physical Oceanography&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Air-sea interacion&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Physical-biogeochemical coupled modelling&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;Education&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;B.Sc&lt;/strong&gt; (2012) in Ocean Sciences, Pusan National University, Busan, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ph.D&lt;/strong&gt; (2020) in Physical Oceanography, Seoul National University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;awards&#34;&gt;Awards&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;9th International Workshop Modeling the Ocean (IWMO) Outstanding Young Scientist Award (2017)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Seo, G.-H., Y.-K. Cho, B.-J. Choi, K.-Y. Kim, Y.-J. Tak (2014), Climate change projection in the Northwestern Pacific marginal seas through dynamic downscaling, J. Geophys. Res., 119(6), 3497-3516.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kwak, H., Y.-K. Cho, G.-H. Seo, Y.-J. Tak, H.-S. Park, S. H. You, J.-W. Seo (2015), Seasonal Sea Surface Temperature Asymmetry in the Northwestern Pacific Marginal Seas, Terr. Atmos. Ocean. Sci., 26(3), 331-340.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tak, Y.-J., Y.-K. Cho, G.-H. Seo, B.-J. Choi (2016), Evolution of wind-driven flows in the Yellow Sea during winter, J. Geophys. Res., 121(3), 1970-1983.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tak, Y.-J., Y.-K. Cho, S. Nam, Numerical investigation of the generation of continental shelf waves and their role in the westward shift of the Yellow Sea Warm Current, Prog. Oceanogr., 187, 102404.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heesung Chong</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/heesungchong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/heesungchong/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-interests&#34;&gt;Research interests&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Remote sensing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Trace gas retrievals&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty estimation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;Education&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ph.D.&lt;/strong&gt; (2021) in Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;B.Sc&lt;/strong&gt; (2015) in Chemical and Biomolecular Engineering, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;awards&#34;&gt;Awards&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Group Achievement Award, 2017.08, NASA &amp;ldquo;KORUS-AQ: An International Cooperative Air Quality Field Study in Korea&amp;rdquo; project&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Koo, J. H., Kim, J., Lee, Y. G., Park, S. S., Lee, S., Chong, H., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Lee, T. (2020). The implication of the air quality pattern in South Korea after the COVID-19 outbreak. Scientific reports, 10(1), 1-11.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chong, H., Lee, S., Kim, J., Jeong, U., Li, C., Krotkov, N. A., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Koo, J. H. (2020). High-resolution mapping of SO2 using airborne observations from the GeoTASO instrument during the KORUS-AQ field study: PCA-based vertical column retrievals. Remote Sensing of Environment, 241, 111725.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Park, H. J., Park, J. S., Kim, S. W., Chong, H., Lee, H., Kim, H., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Park, S. S. (2019). Retrieval of NO2 column amounts from ground-based hyperspectral imaging sensor measurements. Remote Sensing, 11(24), 3005.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chong, H., H. Lee, J. H. Koo, J. Kim, U. Jeong, W. Kim, S. W. Kim, J. R. Herman, N. K. Abuhassan, J. Y. Ahn, J. H. Park, S. K. Kim, K. J. Moon, W. J. Choi, and S. S. Park (2018), Regional characteristics of NO2 column densities from Pandora observations during the MAPS-Seoul campaign, Aerosol and Air Quality Research.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seoyoung Lee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/seoyounglee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eng/people/seoyounglee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-interests&#34;&gt;Research interests&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Retrieval of aerosols and trace gases from satellite or airborne based remote sensing measurements&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Estimation of the long-range transport of aerosols&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Radiative transfer model&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;Education&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ph.D.&lt;/strong&gt; (2021) in Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;B.Sc&lt;/strong&gt; (2015) in Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;awards&#34;&gt;Awards&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Group Achievement Award, 2017.08, NASA &amp;ldquo;KORUS-AQ: An International Cooperative Air Quality Field Study in Korea&amp;rdquo; project&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lee, S., Kim, M., Kim, S. Y., Lee, D. W., Lee, H., Kim, J., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Liu, Y. (2021). Assessment of long-range transboundary aerosols in Seoul, South Korea from Geostationary Ocean Color Imager (GOCI) and ground-based observations. Environmental Pollution, 269, 115924.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Koo, J. H., Kim, J., Lee, Y. G., Park, S. S., Lee, S., Chong, H., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Lee, T. (2020). The implication of the air quality pattern in South Korea after the COVID-19 outbreak. Scientific reports, 10(1), 1-11.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Choi, M., Lim, H., Kim, J., Lee, S., Eck, T. F., Holben, B. N., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Liu, H. (2019). Validation, comparison, and integration of GOCI, AHI, MODIS, MISR, and VIIRS aerosol optical depth over East Asia during the 2016 KORUS-AQ campaign. Atmospheric Measurement Techniques, 12(8), 4619-4641.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lee, S., Kim, J., Choi, M., Hong, J., Lim, H., Eck, T. F., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Koo, J. H. (2019). Analysis of long-range transboundary transport (LRTT) effect on Korean aerosol pollution during the KORUS-AQ campaign. Atmospheric Environment, 204, 53-67.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lee, S., Hong, J., Cho, Y., Choi, M., Kim, J., Park, S. S., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Koo, J. H. (2018). Characteristics of classified aerosol types in south korea during the maps-seoul campaign. Aerosol and Air Quality Research, 18(9), 2195-2206.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kim, S. W., Natraj, V., Lee, S., Kwon, H. A., Park, R., Gouw, J. D., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Warneke, C. (2018). Impact of high-resolution a priori profiles on satellite-based formaldehyde retrievals. Atmospheric Chemistry and Physics, 18(10), 7639-7655.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lee, S., Choi, M., Kim, J., Kim, M., and Lim, H.: Retrieval of Aerosol Optical Depth with High Spatial Resolution using GOCI Data, Korean Journal of Remote Sensing, Vol.33, No.6-1, 2017.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
